[{"question":"If ___ were a color, which color would they be?","answers":["Lime green","Shocking pink","Basic black","Beige","Royal blue","Pure white"]},{"question":"If ___ were a 70's movie, which would it be?","answers":["Love Story","Star Wars","Jaws","The Godfather","Kramer vs. Kramer","Saturday Night Fever"]},{"question":"If ___ were a power source, wich would they be?","answers":["Wind","Solar","Steam","9-volt battery","Coal","Nuclear"]},{"question":"If ___ could only watch one TV show, which would it be?","answers":["The X-Files","Baywatch","Seinfeld","Oprah","60 Minutes","Melrose Place"]},{"question":"If ___ were an 80's movie, which would they be?","answers":["Terminator","Fatal Attraction","Amadeus","Wall Street","E.T.","On Golden Pond"]},{"question":"If ___ were honked at by an impatient driver, how would they react?","answers":["Get out of the car and threaten the driver","Ignore it and turn up the radio","Honk 'em right back","Wink and lick the window","Give a genuine apologetic wave","Record the license plate and call the police"]},{"question":"If ___ were a famous author, who would they be?","answers":["Stephen King","Tom Clancy","Stephen Hawking","Agatha Christie","Jackie Collins","Charles Dickens"]},{"question":"If ___ were a store manager, which store would it be?","answers":["Dairy Queen","Victoria's Secret","Burger King","K Mart","All For A Dollar","Banana Republic"]},{"question":"If ___ had to grant government approval for a major city project, which would they choose?","answers":["Hospital","Library","Casino","Sports stadium","Botanical gardens","Skyscraper"]},{"question":"If ___ were a country, which would they be?","answers":["Turkey","Columbia","France","Iceland","Canada","Bangladesh"]},{"question":"If ___ were a car, which would they be?","answers":["Family sedan","Pick-up truck","Rolls Royce","Red Ferrari","Volkswagon Beetle","Dune Buggy"]},{"question":"If ___ were a war or a battle, which would they be?","answers":["Battle of the bulge","War of words","Battle of the sexes","Crusades","Cold War","Star Wars"]},{"question":"If ___ could be brilliant at one thing, which would they choose?","answers":["Cooking","Gambling","Building","Creating","Romancing","Spelling"]},{"question":"If ___ had to do one scary thing, which would frighten them most?","answers":["Bungee jumping","Addressing the U.N. General Assembly","Catching a tarantula","Asking a secret love on a date","Dining with the in-laws","Becoming a parent"]},{"question":"If ___ were a dental procedure, which would they be?","answers":["Cosmetic whitening","Regular check-up","Gold tooth","Root canal","Braces","Dentures"]},{"question":"If ___ were a condiment, which would they be?","answers":["Salt","Grey Poupon","Vinegar","Ketchup","Tabasco sauce","Powdered rhinoceros horn"]},{"question":"If ___ were a tool, which would they be?","answers":["Sledge hammer","Pruning shears","Screwdriver","Level","Cocktail mixer","Toenail clippers"]},{"question":"If ___ were an invention, which would they be?","answers":["Penicillin","Laptop","Phonograph","Atomic bomb","Blow dryer","Zipper"]},{"question":"If ___ could have one feature from a famous person, what would it be?","answers":["Einstein's brain","Don King's hair","Betty Davis' eyes","Arnold's biceps","Mick Jagger's lips","Elvis' pelvis"]},{"question":"If ___ could enjoy one of life's little luxuries every day, which would they choose?","answers":["A big, hearty breakfast","An ironed newspaper","A manicure","A maid","Port and a Cuban cigar","An afternoon nap"]},{"question":"If ___ were a stage act, which would they be?","answers":["Poetry reading","Stand-up comic","One man band","Magician","Snake charmer","Belly dancing"]},{"question":"If ___ had to choose one thing as most important, which would they choose?","answers":["Religion","Sports","Money","Friendship","Knowledge","Appearance"]},{"question":"If ___ were an insect, which would they be?","answers":["Louse","Ant","Wasp","Butterfly","Praying mantis","Glow worm"]},{"question":"If ___ were a United States President, which would they be?","answers":["George Bush","Harry Truman","Bill Clinton","Richard Nixon","John F. Kennedy","Abraham Lincoln"]},{"question":"If ___ were awakened in the night by a burglar, what would they do?","answers":["Go back to sleep and rely on insurance","Scream","Wake their partner and demand action","Tackle the burglar to the ground","Sneak out and phone the police","Attempt to counsel the burglar"]},{"question":"If ___ were an animal, which would they be?","answers":["Sheep dog","Chimpanzee","Koala bear","Bull","Panther","Toad"]},{"question":"If ___ were a flying object, which would they be?","answers":["Blimp","Biplane","Glider","Frisbee","Lear Jet","Brick"]},{"question":"If ___ were a member of a threesome, which would it be?","answers":["3 Stooges","3 Tenors","3 Musketeers","3 Wise Men","3 Blind Mice","3 Mile Island"]},{"question":"If ___ were a type a headgear, which would they be?","answers":["Baseball cap","Top hat","Beret","Toupee","Miner's helmet","Virtual reality goggles"]},{"question":"If ___ enjoyed a day in the snow, which would they do?","answers":["Ice fishing","Throw snowballs at strangers","Build a snowman","Head for the lodge bar","Hike across a mountain","Make \"donuts\" in a desolate parking lot"]},{"question":"If ___ were a collection, which would they be?","answers":["Spoons","Live insects","Empty beer cans","Frequent Flyer points","Wedding rings","Credit cards"]},{"question":"If ___ were a breakfast, which would they be?","answers":["Coffee and The Wall Street Journal","Muesli and fruit","Croissant and Cafe Latte","Sausages, bacon and eggs","Vitamin B injections","Pancakes with maple syrup"]},{"question":"If ___ were a body part, which would they be?","answers":["Face","Buttocks","Stomach","Hand","Brain","Mouth"]},{"question":"If ___ were a writing implement, which would they be?","answers":["Fountain pen","Keyboard","Chalk","Ball point pen","Crayon","Spray paint"]},{"question":"If ___ could play in a band, which band would it be?","answers":["The Beatles","Abba","The Spice Girls","The Glenn Miller Band","The Village People","AC/DC"]},{"question":"If ___ were a weapon, which would they be?","answers":["Poison","Squirt gun","Atom bomb","Club","Battle axe","Charm"]},{"question":"If ___ had to live in the 'land of the endless season,' which season would they choose?","answers":["Spring","Summer","Fall","Winter","Football","Duck"]},{"question":"If ___ were traveling on the Space Shuttle, how would they feel?","answers":["Proud","Nauseous","Terrified","Bored","Exhilarated","Weightless"]},{"question":"If ___ were kissing goodnight after a first date, where would they plant it?","answers":["Lips","Back of hand","Cheek","Feet","Ear lobe","Tonsils"]},{"question":"If ___ were a piece of advice, what would it be?","answers":["Trust no-one","Be honest at all times","Never walk under a ladder","Dress for success","Marry a millionaire","Eat all your vegetables"]},{"question":"If ___ had a garden, what would be its predominant feature?","answers":["Weeds","Manicured lawn","Flowers","Concrete","Native trees","Gnomes and fountains"]},{"question":"If ___ were a gift, what would they be?","answers":["Bouquet of roses","Book","Tie","Calendar","Cuff links","Shoe horn"]},{"question":"If ___ were a corporation, which would they be?","answers":["Burger King","American Express","Microsoft","20th Century Fox","Nike","Revlon"]},{"question":"If ___ were a dog, what breed would they be?","answers":["Poodle","Rottweiler","Golden Retriever","Dachshund","St. Bernard","Greyhound"]},{"question":"If ___ were a fictional crime fighter, who would they be?","answers":["Sheriff Andy Taylor","Colombo","MacGyver","Maxwell Smart","James Bond","Sherlock Holmes"]},{"question":"If ___ were a hairstyle, which would they be?","answers":["Beehive","Crew cut","Bowl","Mohawk","Tight bun","Pony tail"]},{"question":"If ___ were a sport, which would they be?","answers":["Golf","Basketball","Ice skating","Boxing","Mud wrestling","Football"]},{"question":"If ___ were a soup, which would they be?","answers":["Split pea","French onion","Won ton","Gazpacho","Chicken noodle","Clam chowder"]},{"question":"If ___ could have dinner with an Olympic champion, who would they choose?","answers":["Brian Boitano","Jessie Owens","Mary Lou Retton","Cassius Clay","Greg Louganis","Bruce Jenner"]},{"question":"If ___ were something worn on the hand, what would they be?","answers":["Brass knuckles","Silk glove","Diamond ring","Rubber glove","Puppet","Mitten"]},{"question":"If ___ were a politically correct phrase, which would they be?","answers":["Differently interesting","Chronologically inflated","Ethically disoriented","Uniquely coordinated","Hygienically provocative","Vertically challenged"]},{"question":"If ___ were a simile, what would it be?","answers":["Dumb as a stump","Hungry as a wolf","Sly as a fox","Proud as a peacock","Grouchy as a bear","Strong as an ox"]},{"question":"If ___ were a surgical operation, which would they be?","answers":["Frontal lobotomy","Face lift","Knee reconstruction","Hip replacement","Vasectomy","Mole removal"]},{"question":"If ___ were a Peanuts character, who would they be?","answers":["Charlie Brown","Snoopy","Lucy","Linus","Pig Pen","Schroeder"]},{"question":"Which movie would ___ dread watching most?","answers":["The Sound Of Music","The English Patient","Conan, The Barbarian","Porky's","Friday the 13th","Anything starring Jim Carrey"]},{"question":"If ___ was a type of footwear, which would they be?","answers":["Flip flops","Jack boots","Stiletto heels","Nikes","Slippers","Ballet shoes"]},{"question":"If ___ were a fashion faux pas, which would they be?","answers":["Black shoes with a brown belt","White shoes after Labor Day","Slip showing","Powder blue leisure suit","Clip on tie","Socks with sandals"]},{"question":"If ___ were an award, what would they be?","answers":["Parent of the year","Academy Award","Olympic gold medal","Miss/Mr Universe","Nobel Prize","MVP"]},{"question":"If ___ were an article of memorabilia, what would they be?","answers":["Elvis' sequined jumpsuit","Babe Ruth's bat","Darth Vader's helmet","Dorothy's ruby slippers","Shakespeare's quill","Lincoln's top-hat"]},{"question":"If ___ were one of the senses, which would they be?","answers":["Touch","Sight","Smell","Hearing","Taste","E.S.P."]},{"question":"If ___ were a light source, which would they be?","answers":["Candle","Sun","Lightning","Flashlight","Lava lamp","Laser beam"]},{"question":"If ___ were a profession, which would they be?","answers":["Astronaut","Photographer","Lawyer","Chef","Model","Brick layer"]},{"question":"If ___ were a member of the Royal Family, who would they be?","answers":["Queen Elizabeth","Prince Charles","Queen Mother","Sarah Ferguson","Princess Diana","Prince Philip"]},{"question":"If ___ were a political quote, which would they be?","answers":["\"I didn't inhale\" (Clinton)","\"The buck stops here\" (Truman)","\"Speak softly and carry a big stick\" (T. Roosevelt)","\"Ask not what your country can do for you...\" (JFK)","\"Religion is the opium of the people\" (Marx)","\"Power is the ultimate Aphrodisiac\" (Kissinger)"]},{"question":"If ___ were a Beatle, who would they be?","answers":["John","Paul","George","Ringo","Volkswagon","Dung"]},{"question":"If ___ were a piece of jewelry, which would they be?","answers":["Diamond ring","Anklet","Stud in nostril","Rolex","Brooch","Earring"]},{"question":"If ___ had a wedding day disaster, which would upset them the most?","answers":["Photos are accidentally destroyed","The bride has a historic bad hair day","The best man loses the wedding ring","The wedding day clashes with the Super Bowl","Torrential rain","Not enough to drink"]},{"question":"If ___ were a holiday, which would they be?","answers":["Valentine's Day","Dyngus Day","Independence Day","New Year's Eve","Mardi Gras","Thanksgiving"]},{"question":"If ___ were a sea creature, which would they be?","answers":["Hammerhead shark","Dolphin","Octopus","Angel fish","Jellyfish","Crab"]},{"question":"If ___ were a feeling, what would they be?","answers":["Angry","Tired","Cheerful","Stressed","Romantic","Bored"]},{"question":"If ___ were the chorus of a song, which would they be?","answers":["\"You're so vain, you prob'ly think this song is about you\"","\"I can't get no satisfaction\"","\"How much is that doggy in the window? The one with the waggly tail.\"","\"Country roads, take me home, to the place I belong\"","\"Red red wine, stay close to me\"","\"Goodness, gracious, great balls of fire!\""]},{"question":"If ___ were a 1950's movie, which would they be?","answers":["The Ten Commandments","Gentlement Prefer Blondes","Father of the Bride","The Wild One","The Greatest Show on Earth","Around the World in 80 Days"]},{"question":"If ___ were on an airplane and the pilot died of a heart attack, what would they do?","answers":["Scream hysterically","Pray","Hold hands with the next person and await instructions","Offer to land the plane","Ring the lawyer on the mobile","Send the meal back and order a bottle of whiskey"]},{"question":"If ___ needed a laugh, who would be most likely to provide it?","answers":["Peter Sellers","Jim Carrey","Dan Quayle","Woody Allen","The Three Stooges","Jerry Seinfeld"]},{"question":"If ___ inherited $100,000, what would they do?","answers":["Donate it to charity","Cash the check in one dollar bills","Dispute the amount","Put an addition on the house","Blow it all on a party","Invest it wisely"]},{"question":"If ___ were buying a home, which of the following would they consider most important?","answers":["Proximity to schools","Spa and sauna","TV reception","Lush garden","Garage/workshop","Proximity to work"]},{"question":"If ___ could keep only one of the following, which would they choose?","answers":["Television","Books","Computer","Telephone","Blow dryer","Wine collection"]},{"question":"If ___ were falsely accused of stealing at work, what would they do?","answers":["Resign in protest","Investigate to expose the real thief","Frame a colleague","Actually steal something in retaliation","Tearfully plead innocence","Sue for slander"]},{"question":"If ___ could have just one pet, which would they choose?","answers":["Pit Bull","Parrot","Poodle","Hamster","Black cat","Pet rock"]},{"question":"If ___ were a manager, what would they consider the most important quality in employees?","answers":["Ruthlessness","Experience","Low pay requirements","Team player","Academic qualifications","Looks"]},{"question":"If ___ moved to a new neighborhood and knew no one, what would they do?","answers":["Keep it that way","Join the local gym","Join the local church","Go to the local bar each Friday night","Throw a party for the neighbors","Hope for the neighbors to make contact"]},{"question":"If ___ had the deciding vote for an Oscar for the greatest ever male actor, who would they choose?","answers":["Tom Cruise","Jack Nicholson","Lawrence Olivier","Spencer Tracy","Arnold Schwarzenegger","David Hasselhof"]},{"question":"If ___ had to sing at a karaoke bar, which song would they sing?","answers":["Blue Suede Shoes","New York, New York","Stand By Your Man","Figaro","I Honestly Love You","Stairway To Heaven"]},{"question":"If ___ were a bad habit, which would they be?","answers":["Breaking wind in public","Winking at people","Gossiping","Continual yawning","Biting finger nails","Constantly looking in the mirror"]},{"question":"If ___ could be one of the following sportsmen, which would they choose?","answers":["John McEnroe","Babe Ruth","Joe Montana","Michael Jordan","Muhammed Ali","Arnold Palmer"]},{"question":"If ___ were a crime, which would they be?","answers":["Vagrancy","Homicide","Shoplifting","Corporate fraud","Unsafe lane change","Indecent exposure"]},{"question":"If ___ had made a million dollars, how would they most like to have made it?","answers":["Sporting prowess","Brilliant invention","Sheer hard work","Class action lawsuit","Winning the lottery","Show business"]},{"question":"If ___ won tickets to a concert, which performance would they rather attend?","answers":["Luciano Pavarotti","Willie Nelson","Laser Floyd","Metallica","Spice Girls","Barry Manilow"]},{"question":"If ___ were a mode of transport, which would they be?","answers":["Hot rod","Pogo stick","Horse and buggy","Time machine","Corporate jet","Jogging"]},{"question":"If ___ were a criminal, who would they be?","answers":["Al Capone","Michael Milken","Heidi Fleiss","Robin Hood","Richard Nixon","The Joker"]},{"question":"If ___ were a city, which would they be?","answers":["Transylvania","New York","Paris","Jerusalem","Las Vegas","Calcutta"]},{"question":"If ___ were a floating vessel, which would they be?","answers":["Gondola","Destroyer","Speed boat","Kayak","Luxury liner","Fishing trawler"]},{"question":"If ___ were propositioned at work by a co-worker they dilikes, what would they do?","answers":["Laugh out loud","Scam a free dinner","Pretend to be married","Sue for harassment","Boast to others in the office","Politely decline"]},{"question":"If ___ could choose a characteristic for their children, which would it be?","answers":["Natural athleticism","Sense of humor","Honesty","Superior intellect","Business smarts","Burning desire to financially support parents"]},{"question":"If ___ were a piece of furniture, which would they be?","answers":["Coffee table","Louis XV antique","Beanbag chair","Ironing board","Bookcase","Water bed"]},{"question":"If ___ were an era, which would they be?","answers":["Biblical era","Computer age","Old West","Decadent Rome","Stone Age","Victorian Era"]},{"question":"If ___ could attend any sporting event, which would they choose?","answers":["U.S. Masters","Wimbledon","Super Bowl","Kentucky Derby","World heavyweight boxing title fight","Monte Carlo Grand Prix"]},{"question":"If ___ spent a relaxing day alone, what would they do?","answers":["Go shopping","Surf the 'net","Watch TV","Meditate","Enjoy the great outdoors","Work on the tan"]},{"question":"If ___ suffered from a phobia, which would it be?","answers":["Ochlophobia (clowns)","Arachnophobia (spiders)","Triskaidekaphobia (thirteen)","Mysophobia (dirt)","Acrophobia (heights)","Nyctophobia (darkness)"]},{"question":"If ___ were to die of a mysterious death, what would it be?","answers":["Abducted by aliens","Choked to death on Jell-O","Killed by a bear","Poisoned by own cooking","Electrocuted while changing a light bulb","Tripping over shoelace"]},{"question":"If ___ won an overseas trip, which country would they visit?","answers":["Kenya","Austria","France","Tahiti","China","Egypt"]},{"question":"If ___ was a musical instrument, which would they be?","answers":["Triangle","Bagpipes","Electric guitar","Saxophone","Violin","Organ"]},{"question":"If ___ could invite a famous historical figure home for dinner, whom would they invite?","answers":["Mother Theresa","Groucho Marx","Richard Nixon","Bill Gates","Marilyn Monroe","Muhammed Ali"]},{"question":"If ___ had to decide the best way to spend New Year's Eve, 1999, what would they choose?","answers":["Go to bed at 9PM with a nice cup of warm milk","Spend the evening alone looking up at the stars and thinking","A quiet celebration with the family","Attend the ballet and thence to a cocktail party","Go to a wild party and pass out at 11:59 PM","Sit by the computer to witness the effect of the millennium bug."]},{"question":"If ___ were an animal sound, which would they be?","answers":["Meow","Moo","Roar","Gobble","Hiss","Hoot"]},{"question":"If ___ were a body of water, which would they be?","answers":["A puddle","An Olympic-sized swimming pool","An ice cube","A Roman bath","A wilderness lake","An ocean"]},{"question":"If ___ were a dessert, which would they be?","answers":["Fresh fruit","Port and cigars","Cheese and coffee","Banana split","Brandied kumquats","Jell-O"]},{"question":"If ___ were a plant, which would they be?","answers":["Towering oak tree","Kudzu","Venus fly trap","Red rose","Ragweed","Dried flower"]},{"question":"If ___ were a board game, which would they be?","answers":["Monopoly","Scrabble","Twister","iMAgiNiff...","Chess","Candy Land"]},{"question":"If ___ had an office plant, what kind would they have?","answers":["Bonsai","Tropical","Fungus","A dead one","Cactus","Plastic"]},{"question":"If ___ were a cable channel, which would they be?","answers":["Comedy Central","CNN","Discovery Channel","ESPN","SyFy Channel","Home Shopping Network"]},{"question":"If ___ were something to sit on, which would they be?","answers":["Throne","Bar stool","Rocking chair","Electric chair","Park bench","Toilet"]},{"question":"If ___ were a musical style, which would they be?","answers":["Classical","Rap","Rock 'n roll","Disco","Jazz","Country and Western"]},{"question":"If ___ were a form of advertisement, which would they be?","answers":["Magazine ad","Endorsement by a sports star","Radio ad","Roadside billboard","Sky writing","Spam e-mail"]},{"question":"If ___ had the deciding vote for an Oscar for the best actress, who would they choose?","answers":["Kathryn Hepburn","Pamela Anderson","Demi Moore","Sharon Stone","Elizabeth Taylor","Marge Simpson"]},{"question":"If ___ were a singer, who would they be?","answers":["Julio Iglesias","Placido Domingo","The Artist Formerly Known as Prince","Dolly Parton","Alice Cooper","Julie Andrews"]},{"question":"If ___ were a cliché, which would they be?","answers":["Wolf in sheep's clothing","Born with a silver spoon in the mouth","Burning the candle at both ends","At one with nature","Look what the cat dragged in","A sight for sore eyes"]},{"question":"If ___ were on a 10-hour car trip, which would upset them the most?","answers":["Being stuck behind a little old lady travelling at 30 MPH","Running over a bunny rabbit","Children fighting in the back seat","A small scratch on the paint work","Sound system breaks down","Mobile phone goes out of range"]},{"question":"If ___ were sporting equipment, which would they be?","answers":["Bowling pin","Hockey puck","Putter","Javelin","Shoulder pads","Mouth guard"]},{"question":"If ___ were a book, which would they be?","answers":["How to Win Friends and Influence People","Alice in Wonderland","A Brief History of Time","Lady Chatterley's Lover","The Shining","The Bible"]},{"question":"If ___ were thirsty, which would they prefer to drink?","answers":["Beer","Mineral water","Piña colada","Orange juice","Cola","1954 Chateaux Lafitte Rothschild"]},{"question":"If ___ were a dance, which would they be?","answers":["Tango","Square","Waltz","Break","Disco","Polka"]},{"question":"If ___ were a superhero, who would they be?","answers":["Superman","The Incredible Hulk","The Phantom","Aqua Man","Batman","Wonder Woman"]},{"question":"If ___ bought a newspaper, which would they read first?","answers":["Personals","Financial section","Sports","Comics","Obituaries","Want ads"]},{"question":"If ___ were a world record, which would they be?","answers":["The world's largest piggy bank","The world's longest sausage","The world's largest ball of twine","Juggling the most objects while running","The world's hottest chili pepper","The world's most dense substance"]},{"question":"If ___ were a room, which would they be?","answers":["Study","Kitchen","Wine cellar","Bedroom","Bathroom","Darkroom"]},{"question":"If ___ had to decide which of the following events most concerned them, which would they choose?","answers":["Beatles break-up","Soup getting cold","Michael Jordan quitting basketball","Michael Jackson's hair catching fire","1987 stock market crash","The Exxon-Valdez oil spill"]},{"question":"If ___ were a type of confection, which would they be?","answers":["M&M's","Gum","Cotton candy","Breath mint","Chocolate liqueur","Jelly bean"]},{"question":"If ___ had to select a way of dying, which would they choose?","answers":["Peacefully in sleep","Hit by a golf ball","Fighting in a war","Murdered by a jealous lover","TV falls into bubble bath","Overeating"]},{"question":"If ___ were a historic disaster, which would they be?","answers":["Sinking of the Titanic","Bubonic Plague","Crash of the Hindenburg","Stock market crash","Noah's flood","Eruption of Mount St. Helens"]},{"question":"If ___ were to be honored, which of the following would they be happiest to accept?","answers":["A papel blessing","Cornerstone on a community center","Good Housekeeping seal of approval","Life review on 60 Minutes","Cash award","A race horse named after them"]},{"question":"If ___ were a 1990's movie, which would it be?","answers":["Independence Day","Pulp Fiction","The English Patient","Forrest Gump","Pretty Woman","There's Something About Mary"]},{"question":"If ___ were going on a picnic, which would they consider essential?","answers":["Sandwich and coffee","Champagne and caviar","Laptop and mobile phone","Loud radio","A bat and ball","A good book"]},{"question":"If ___ were a 1960's movie, which would they be?","answers":["Barbarella","The Sound of Music","2001 - A Space Odyssey","Goldfinger","Psycho","Dr. Zhivago"]},{"question":"If ___ were an author, what type of books would they write?","answers":["Children's","Science fiction","Romance","Thriller","Whodunits","Basket-weaving textbooks"]},{"question":"If ___ belonged to a a TV family, which would it be?","answers":["The Simpsons","The Ewings","The Brady Bunch","The Cartwrights","The Flintstones","The Addams Family"]},{"question":"If ___ were an entrée, which would they be?","answers":["Big Mac","Duck à l'orange","Spaghetti and meatballs","Stuffed turkey","Canned ham","Buffalo wings"]},{"question":"If ___ had time to do only one of the following every morning, which would they choose?","answers":["Exercise","Read the newspaper","Eat a big breakfast","Meditate","Have a massage","Play with the children"]},{"question":"If ___ were a monster, which would they be?","answers":["Dracula","The Blob","Frankenstein","Werewolf","Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde","Cookie Monster"]},{"question":"If ___ were a sports penalty, what would they be?","answers":["Hooking","Balk","Hitting below the belt","Charging","Clipping","Unsportsmanlike conduct"]},{"question":"If ___ were the subject of a photograph, what form would it take?","answers":["Police mug shot","Pulling a funny face","Bikini-clad","Sporting pose","Seated, formally dressed","Cover of The Enquirer"]},{"question":"If ___ were a toy, which would they be?","answers":["Barbie doll","Chemistry set","Teddy bear","Magic set","Transformers","Play-Doh"]},{"question":"If ___ awoke to find the house in flames, which would they save first?","answers":["Insurance policy","Favorite shoes","Family photos","Cash","Self portrait","Sports equipment"]},{"question":"If ___ accidentally emitted an unpleasant anti-social noise at a dinner party, what would they do?","answers":["Say nothing and blush brightly","Apologize","Laugh and repeat the offense (louder, if possible)","Blame the person sitting next to them","Try to re-produce the sound by shifting in their seat","Carry on as if nothing happened"]},{"question":"If ___ was an Olympic event, which would they be?","answers":["100 meter sprint","Boxing","Beach volleyball","Weightlifting","Luge","Marathon"]},{"question":"If ___ were an article of clothing, which would they be?","answers":["Pin-striped suit","Prison uniform","Pajamas","Sweat pants","Faded jeans","Mini skirt"]},{"question":"If ___ were a cartoon character, who would they be?","answers":["George Jetson","Wile E. Coyote","Daffy Duck","Tweety Bird","Underdog","Homer Simpson"]},{"question":"If ___ were a form of communication, which would they be?","answers":["Telephone","Mental telepathy","Body language","E-mail","Car horn","Smoke signal"]},{"question":"If ___ were a comic strip character, who would they be?","answers":["Dilbert","Blondie","Dennis the Menace","Popeye","Hagar the Horrible","Andy Capp"]},{"question":"If ___ were a musician, which would they be?","answers":["Liberace","Weird Al Yankovic","Snoop Doggy Dog","Jimi Hendrix","Madonna","Billy Joel"]},{"question":"If ___'s doctor suggested more exercise, which would they do?","answers":["Triathlon","Pump iron","Power walk","Yoga","Disco aerobics","Seek a second opinion"]},{"question":"If ___ could go on a dream vacation, which would it be?","answers":["Disney World","Luxury cruise","Visit the world's great museums","African hunting safari","Work aorund the house","Spend all day every day surfing the internet"]},{"question":"If ___ accidentally backed over the neighbor's cat in the driveway, which would they do?","answers":["Bury it and say nothing","Confess","Buy a replacement and pretend nothing happened","Place it on the road and say nothing","Blame the neighbor for inadequate cat control","Run over it again to make sure it was dead"]},{"question":"If ___ were an emotion, which would they be?","answers":["Hate","Fear","Jealousy","Rage","Lust","Love"]},{"question":"If ___ were a special vehicle, which would they be?","answers":["Tank","Ambulance","Parade float","Garbage truck","Ice cream truck","Limousine"]},{"question":"If ___ were a superlative, which would they be?","answers":["Easiest","Cheesiest","Smoothest","Sleepiest","Goofiest","Sweetest"]},{"question":"If ___'s personality were a male nickname, which would be best?","answers":["Romeo","Marvin","Conan","Todd","Jeremiah","Elvis"]},{"question":"If ___ were a timepiece, which would they be?","answers":["Stopwatch","Biological clock","Grandfather clock","Oven timer","Sundial","Time bomb"]},{"question":"If ___ were an Olympic site, which would they be?","answers":["Barcelona","Los Angeles","Berlin","Ancient Athens","Mexico City","Lake Placid"]},{"question":"If ___ could travel in a time machine, which event would they choose to witness?","answers":["The Rumble in the Jungle (Ali vs. Foreman - Zaire - 1974)","The apple falling on Newton's head","Moses parting the Red Sea","Elvis' first live performance","Their own birth","Next year's Kentucky Derby"]},{"question":"If ___'s personality were a female name, which would be best?","answers":["Mary Lou","Helga","Brigitte","Xena","Bubbles","Prudence"]},{"question":"If ___ were a kind a metal, which would they be?","answers":["Gold","Bronze","Titanium","Cast iron","Quicksilver","Heavy metal"]},{"question":"If ___ were a character from Star Wars, which would they be?","answers":["Luke Skywalker","Princess Leia","Master Yoda","Chewbacca","C-3PO","Darth Vader"]},{"question":"If ___ was a display of friendship, which would they be?","answers":["Lingering kiss","Hug","Firm handshake","Wink","High five","Slap on the back"]},{"question":"If ___ witnessed a mugging on the city street, what would they do?","answers":["Wrestle the mugger to the ground","Ignore it and keep walking","Attempt a citizen's arrest","Offer post-mugging counseling","Scream hysterically","Take a photo and sell it to the media"]},{"question":"If ___ were a movie catchphrase, which would they be?","answers":["\"Here's looking at you, kid\"","\"Go ahead, make my day\"","\"May the force be with you\"","\"A martini, shaken, not stirred\"","\"There's no place like home\"","\"This is another fine mess you've gotten me into\""]},{"question":"If ___ could discover the answer to a great mystery, which mystery would they choose?","answers":["Who killed JFK?","What are the Colonel's eleven secret herbs and spices?","Is there life in outer space?","What is the secret of eternal youth and good looks?","How come I pay more taxes than Donald Trump?","What happens after death?"]},{"question":"If ___ could afford to buy a dream home, which would they buy?","answers":["Ultra-modern city penthouse","Sprawling farmhouse","Grand mansion","Rugged mountain lodge","Beach condominium","Medieval castle"]},{"question":"If ___ could acquire one of the following natural abilities, which would they choose?","answers":["Amazing eye/hand coordination","The ability to contact the spirit world","Photographic memory","The ability to win friends and influence people","Musical virtuosity","Optimism"]},{"question":"If ___ were a high school class, which would they be?","answers":["Social Studies","Home Economics","Shop","Lunch","Gym","Study Hall"]},{"question":"If ___ suffered a minor crisis, which would upset them most?","answers":["Burning the roast","Scratch on the car","Computer virus","TV breaking down","Credit cards cancelled","Stain on the lapel"]},{"question":"If ___ were choosing hotel accommodations, which of the following would they deem most important?","answers":["The name","The size of the bed","Cleanliness","The price","Number of cable TV channels","Well-stocked mini bar"]},{"question":"If ___ were at a construction site, what would they be doing?","answers":["Setting up cones","Taking a coffee break","Drawing up the plans","Getting fired","Doing something with a jack-hammer","Complaining about working conditions"]},{"question":"If ___ could solve one problem, which would they choose?","answers":["Computer viruses","War","Unemployment","Environmental destruction","Immorality","The disco revival"]},{"question":"If ___ were something to look through, which would they be?","answers":["Telescope","Sunglasses","Reading glasses","Binoculars","Safety goggles","Rose-colored glasses"]},{"question":"If ___ were a circus performer, which would they be?","answers":["Clown","Trapeze artist","Lion tamer","Juggler","Fire eater","Performing poodle"]},{"question":"If ___ were a famous landmark, which would they be?","answers":["Empire State Building","Taj Mahal","The \"Hollywood\" sign","Leaning Tower of Pisa","Yankee Stadium","Stonehenge"]},{"question":"If ___ were a home, which would they be?","answers":["4 bedroom, brick with family room","Mobile home","Penthouse apartment","Beach house","Tent","Grand mansion"]},{"question":"If ___ were a decade, which would they be?","answers":["Politically correct '90s","Greedy '80s","Groovy '70s","Swinging '60s","Conservative '50s","Roaring '20s"]},{"question":"If ___ were a TV catchphrase, which would they be?","answers":["\"Beam me up, Scotty\"","\"Doh!\"","\"And now for something completely different\"","\"Who loves ya baby\"","\"And loving it!\"","\"Your mission, should you choose to accept it...\""]},{"question":"If ___ stepped onto a bus and the only other passenger was their favorite TV star, what would they do?","answers":["Ignore the star","Politely say hello but respect their privacy","Tell the star about a great creative","Offer a critique of the star's work","Nervously ask for an autograph","Drop their jaw and scream \"I love you!\""]},{"question":"If ___ were a magazine, which would they be?","answers":["Time","Sports Illustrated","Popular Science","House and Garden","Vogue","MAD"]},{"question":"If ___ were an advertising slogan, which would they be?","answers":["\"Breakfast of champions\"","\"Think different\"","\"A diamond is forever\"","\"Where's the beef?\"","\"Not going anywhere for a while?\"","\"Have it your way\""]},{"question":"If ___ were a flavor of ice cream, which would they be?","answers":["Plain vanilla","Rocky road","Sweet cream","Dark chocolate","Strawberry cheesecake","Nut crunch"]}]